♪ Ah push it ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Ooh, baby, baby, baby, baby ♪
♪ Ooh, baby, baby,
ba-baby, baby ♪
♪ Get up on this ♪
♪ Ah, push it ♪
♪ Ow! Baby! ♪
♪ Salt-N-Pepa's here ♪
♪ Salt, Salt-Salt,
Salt-N-Pepa's here ♪
♪ Salt-Salt-Salt-Salt,
Salt-n-Pepa's here ♪
♪ Salt-n-Pepa, Salt-n-Pepa,
♪ Salt-Salt-Salt,
Salt-n-Pepa's here ♪
♪ Now, now, now,
wait a minute y'all ♪
♪ This dance ain't
for everybody ♪
♪ Only the sexy people ♪
♪ So all you fly mother's,
get on out there and dance ♪
♪ Dance, I said ♪
♪ Salt-n-Pepa's here,
and we're in effect ♪
♪ Want you to push it back ♪
♪ Cooling by day, then at
night, working up a sweat ♪
♪ C'mon girls, let's go
show the guys that we know ♪
♪ How to become number
one in a hot party show ♪
♪ Now push it ♪
♪ Push it good ♪
♪ (Ah, push it)
push it real good ♪
♪ (Ah, push it) push it good ♪
♪ (Ah, push it)
p-push it real good ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Ow! ♪
♪ Push it good ♪
♪ Ooh, baby, baby, baby, baby ♪
♪ Ooh, baby, baby,
ba-baby, baby ♪
♪ Push it good ♪
♪ Push it real good ♪
♪ Ah, push it ♪
♪ Yo, yo, yo, yo, baby-pop ♪
♪ Yeah, you! Come
here, gimme a kiss ♪
♪ Better make it fast or
else I'm gonna get pissed ♪
♪ Can't you hear the
music pumping hard? ♪
♪ Like I wish you would ♪
♪ Now push it ♪
♪ Push it good ♪
♪ Push it real good ♪
♪ P-push it real good ♪
♪ Ah, push it ♪
♪ Get up on this ♪
♪ (Uh) get up on this ♪
♪ (Uh, uh) get up on this ♪
♪ (Ha) get up on this ♪
♪ (Hit it) ♪
♪ Boy, you really got me going ♪
♪ You got me so ♪
♪ I don't know what I'm doing ♪
♪ Ah, push it ♪
♪ Boy, you really got me going ♪
♪ You got me so ♪
♪ I don't know what I'm doing ♪
♪ Ah, push it ♪
♪♪♪
♪ Ah ♪
♪ Ah, push it ♪
♪ Push-push-push-push
it, push it ♪
♪ Push it ♪
♪ Push, push, push,
push it, push it ♪
♪ Push it, push it ♪
♪ Push it, push it, push it ♪